Guide to the Grigori Mints Papers SC1225
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Grigori Mints papers
1954-2014
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Mints, Grigori
SC1225
57.25 Linear Feet (44 boxes)
Information about Access
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Marianna Rozenfeld, 2014 & Evelyn McMillan, 2015.
Philosophy.; Philosophy -- Study and teaching.; Research -- Philosophy.; Logic, Symbolic and Mathematical.; Mathematics -- Philosophy.; Logicians -- United States -- Biography.; Mints, Grigori
- Email (print-outs), 1990-2014
  - 1990-1994 (Box 1)
  - 1995-1998 (Box 2)
  - 1998-2000 (Box 3)
  - 2000-2012 (Box 4)
  - 1994-2001 (Box 5)
  - Foundations of Mathematics (FOM) digest, 2002-2011 (Box 5)
  - Friedman, Harvey; Foundations of Mathematics (FOM) digest, 2003-2010 (Box 42)
- Conferences
  - Russian
    - Conference proceedings, 1976-2001 (Box 26)
    - 2012 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - English
    - Conference Materials from St. Petersberg, 2014 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Philosophy, Mathematics, Linguistics: Aspects of Interaction, 2009 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Documents, undated (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Association for Symbolic Logic, 1997-2011 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Joint Mathematics Meetings, 2012 Jan. 4-7 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Collegium Logicum - Cut-Elimination, 2005 Jul. 4-6 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Mathematics - XXI Century - PDMI 70th Anniversary, 2010 Sep. 13-18 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - MFCS & CSL, 2010 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Lecture Notes in Logic, 1974, 1990, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - The Rolf Schock Prizes, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Universality of Science, 1995-1996 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Methods of Logic in Mathematics III, 2006 Jun. 1-7 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - European Foundation for Logic, Language and Information, 1992 Aug. (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - BRICS Proof Theory and Complexity, 1998 Aug. 3-7 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - First International Wormshop, 2012 Apr. 16-19 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Mathematische Logik, 1998 Jan. 18-24 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Proof Theory: Workshop on Logic, Foundational Research, and Mathematics, 2003 Oct. 9-11 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Model Computation - Principles, Algorithms, Applications, 6/16/2000 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - 1st North American Summer School in Logic, Language, and Information, 2002 Jun. 24-30 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - WoLLIC 2005 Proceedings, 2005 Jul. 19-22 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - ILCLI, 1993-2003 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Takeuti Symposium, 2003 Dec. 17-19 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Natural Deduction, 2001 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - WoLLIC, 2006 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Conferences, 2006 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Logic in the Netherlands, 1998 Feb. (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Banff International Research Station, 2007 Feb. 18-23 (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Shell Oil Symposium Series, 11/5/1995 (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - 9th International Conogress of Logic, Methodology, and Philosophy of Science, 1991 Aug. 7-14 (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - 10th International Conogress of Logic, Methodology, and Philosophy of Science, 1995 Aug. 19-25 (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - Nato ASI Report, 1993 Aug. 13-24 (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - Godel's Excursions Into Intuitionistic Logic, 1983 Jul. 10-12 (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - Summer School and Conference on Mathematical Logic, 1988 Sep. 13-23 (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - Logic Colloquium, 2004 Jul. 25-31 (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - Logic Colloquium, 1990 Jul. 15-22 (Box 27, Folder 35)
    - Computer Science Logic, 1992 Jul. 13-17 (Box 27, Folder 36)
    - Proof Theory and Algorithms Workshops, 2003 Mar. 23-28 (Box 27, Folder 37)
    - DAYS Shanin, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 38)
    - Markov, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 39)
    - CSR, 2006 (Box 27, Folder 40)
    - Mathematische Logik, 1995 Apr. 2-8 (Box 27, Folder 41)
    - HPLMC-02, 2002 Nov. 7-9 (Box 27, Folder 42)
    - Nasslli, 2003 Jun. 17-21 (Box 27, Folder 43)
    - Classical Logic and Computation, 2010 (Box 27, Folder 44)
    - Symbolic Logic and Computer Science, 1995 Sep. 17-20 (Box 27, Folder 45)
    - Logic colloquium, Berlin, 1989 (Box 28)
    - Colloquium on Modal Logic, 1991 (Box 28)
    - 1992 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - 1992-1994 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - 1994 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - 1994-1995 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - 1994-1999 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Logic colloquium, 1995 Aug 9-17 (Box 28)
    - 1995 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - 1996 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - International Conference TABLEAUX'97-Analytic Tableaux and Related Methods, 1997-03 (Box 28)
    - 1997 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Logic in Action: An NWO Spinoza Award Project, 1997-1998 (Box 28)
    - 1998 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - 17th International Conference on Automated Deduction, Carnegie Mellon University, 2000 Jun 17-20 (Box 28)
    - Constructivism in Non-Classical Logics and Computer Science, 2000 Sep 30-Oct 2 (Box 28)
    - LCCS'2001: Proceedings of the International Workshop on Logic and Complexity in Computer Science, Universite Paris, France, 2001 Sep 3-5 (Box 28)
    - Logic-Based Program Synthesis: State of the Art and Future Trends, 2002 AAAI Spring Symposium (Box 28)
    - Conference in Honor of the 60th Birthday of Friedman, Harvey M., 2009 May 14-17 (Box 28)
    - Leeds Symposium on Proof Theory and Constructivism, 2009 Jul 3-16 (Box 28)
    - Algebra and Coalgebra meet Proof Theory, 2013 (Box 28)
- Department files
  - CAST, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Funding, 1994-2008 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Feferman, Solomon symposium, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - DTL, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Drafts, 1992-2009 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Dept, 2008 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Dept, 2005-2006 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - 2005 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Computer Science Department, 2006 (Box 30, Folder 9)
- Publications
  - Index cards (English and Russian) (Box 22-23)
    Scope and Contents note
    Arranged alphabetically publications index.
  - GM published articles in Russian, undated (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - A Normal Form Theorem For Second-Order Classical Logic with an Axiom of Choice (2 copies), 1989 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - A normal form for logical derivations implying one for arithmetic derivations (2 copies), 1993 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - A New Reduction Sequence for Arithmetic, undated (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - A New Reduction Sequence for Arithmetic, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Development and present state of epsilon substitution method, undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Beklemisher's construction of Eo Stanford talk, undated (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Abstract for Banff, 2007 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Model elimination and cut elimination, undated (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Abstract for Contibuted Talk, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - BSL 3, N3 Winter Meeting of the Association for Symbolic Logic, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Bull. ASL V1.N3 Winter Meeting of the Association for Symbolic Logic, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - A Completeness Proof for Propositional S4 in Cantor Space (2 copies), 2001 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - ADC Method of Proof Search for Intuitonistic Prepositional Natural Deduction, 2012 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Admissible and Derived Rules, undated (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - An Approach to an e-Substitution Method dor ID1, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Applications of Proof-theoretic Transformation (Abstract), 1998 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - A proof of topological completeness for S4 in (0,1) (2 copies), 2004 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - A simple proof of second-order strong normalization with permutative conversions (2 copies), 2005 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - A simple proof of the coherence theorem fro Cartesian closed categories, undated (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - A termination proof for epsilon substitution using partial derivations (3 copies), 2003 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Applications of Proof-theoretic Transformation (Abstract), 1998 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Axiomatization of a Skolem Function in Intuitionistic Logic (3 copies), 2000 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Classical and Intuitionistic Geometric Logic (3 copies), 2012 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Logical Investigations (2 copies), 2000 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Closed Categories and the Theory of Proofs, undated (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Closed Categories and the Theory of Proofs (office copy), 1992 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Completeness of Indexed e-Calculus (2 copies), 2003 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Complexity of Subclasses of the Intuitionistic Propositional Calculus (2 copies), 1990 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Condensed Detachment is Complete for Relevance Logic: A Computer-Aided Proof, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Corrigenda and Addenda to the Article "On Predicate and Operator Variants of the Formation of the Theories of Constructive Mathematics", 1967 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Cut-elimination and Normal Forms of Sequent Derivations, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Cut elimination for a simple formulation of epsilon calculus (2 copies), 2007 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Cut Elimination for S4C: A Case Study, 2006 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Abstracts of the AMS, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Cut-Elimination for Simple Type Theory with an Axiom of Choice (3 copies), 1999 (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Cute-Free Calculi of the S5 Type (3 copies), undated (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Cut-Free Formulations for a quantified logic of here and there, 2010 (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Decidability of the Class 3 by Maslov's Inverse Method, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Decidability of the Class 3 by Maslov's Inverse Method, 2010 (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Disjunctive interpretation of the LJ-Calculus e.u. Implicative complexity of axiomatics, undated (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - Epsilon Substitution for Predicate Logic, 2010 (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - Epsilon substitution method for elementary analysis, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - Epsilon substitution method for elementary analysis, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 44)
  - Epsilon-Substitution Method for Ramified Language and Comprehension Rule (2 copies), 1999 (Box 25, Folder 45)
  - Existential Instantiation and Strong Normalization, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 46)
  - Theoretical Computer Science: Extended normal form theorems for logical proofs from axioms (2 copies), 2000 (Box 25, Folder 47)
  - J Soviet Math 8, N3, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 48)
  - Exact Estimates of the Provability of Transfinite Induction in the Initial Segments of Arithmetic, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 49)
  - Failure of Interpolation in Constant Domain Intuitionistic Logic (2 copies), 2013 (Box 25, Folder 50)
  - Finite Investigations of Transfinite Derivations, undated (Box 25, Folder 51)
  - Fixing Frege, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 52)
  - Failure of Interpolation in Constant Domain Intuitionistic Logic (2 copies), 2013 (Box 25, Folder 53)
  - Justification of the Structural Synthesis of Programs, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 54)
  - Interpolation Theorems for intuitionistic predicate logic (2 copies), 2002 (Box 25, Folder 55)
  - In Memoriam: Albert G. Dragalin (10 copies), 1999 (Box 25, Folder 56)
  - Indexed Systems of Sequents and Cut-Elimination (2 Copies), 1997 (Box 25, Folder 57)
  - Implicative Complexity of Axiomatic Systems, undated (Box 25, Folder 58)
  - Heyting Predicate Calculus with Epsilon Symbol, undated (Box 25, Folder 59)
  - Herbrand's Theorem for the Predicate Calculus with Equality and Functional Symbols (3 copies), 1966 (Box 25, Folder 60)
  - Gentzen-Type Systems and Resolution Rule Part II. Predicate Logic, undated (Box 25, Folder 61)
  - Lecture Notes in Computer Science, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 62)
  - Gentzen-Type Systems and Hilbert's Epsilon Substitution Method. I (2 copies), 1994 (Box 25, Folder 63)
  - Selected Papers in Proof Theory, Bibliopolis and North-Holland p. 221-294 (2 copies), 1992 (Box 25, Folder 64)
  - Linear Lambda-Terms and Natural Deduction (2 copies), 1998 (Box 25, Folder 65)
  - Logical Equations in Monadic Logic (3 copies), 2008 (Box 25, Folder 66)
  - Mechanical Proof-Search and the Theory of Logical Deduction in the USSR, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 67)
  - New Trends in Foundations of Mathematics, 2009 (Box 25, Folder 68)
  - Nikolai Aleksandrovich Shanin (obituary) (3 copies), 2013 (Box 25, Folder 69)
  - Normal Forms for Sequent Derivations (2 copies), undated (Box 25, Folder 70)
  - Email with Subject: Contraction in Sequent Derivations, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 71)
  - Normal Deduction in the Intuitionistic Linear Logic (2 copies), 1996 (Box 25, Folder 72)
  - Normalization of Finite Terms and Derivations via Infinite Ones (3 copies), 1992 (Box 25, Folder 73)
  - Normalization Theorems for the Intuitionistic Systems (2 copies), 1990 (Box 25, Folder 74)
  - Notes on Constructive Negation (4 copies), 2006 (Box 25, Folder 75)
  - Normal Forms for Sequent Derivations, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 76)
  - Normalization of Finite Terms and Derivations via Infinite Ones, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 77)
  - on E-Theorems (2 copies), undated (Box 25, Folder 78)
  - On Novikov's Hypothesis, undated (Box 25, Folder 79)
  - On Some Calculi of Modal Logic, undated (Box 25, Folder 80)
  - On the Construction of Conservative Logical Deductions, undated (Box 25, Folder 81)
  - On the Semantics of Modal Logic (2 copies), 1971 (Box 25, Folder 82)
  - Proof Search Tree and Cut-Elimination, undated (Box 25, Folder 83)
  - Proof Theory and Category Theory, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 84)
  - Formal Systems for Classical Analysis, undated (Box 25, Folder 85)
  - Proof Theory in the USSR (2 copies), 1991 (Box 25, Folder 86)
  - Propositional logic of continuous transformations in Cantor space (2 copies), 2004 (Box 25, Folder 87)
  - Propositional Logic Programming, undated (Box 25, Folder 88)
  - Proof Theory in the USSR, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 89)
  - Propositional Logic Programming, undated (Box 25, Folder 90)
  - Propositional Logic Programming and the Priz System, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 91)
  - Quantifier-Free and One-Quantifier Systems, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 92)
  - Reduction of finite and infinite derivations, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 93)
  - The Programming System PRIZ, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 94)
  - Thoraf Skolem and the Epsilon Substitution Method for Predicate Logic (2 copies), 1996 (Box 25, Folder 95)
  - The Completeness of Structural Synthesis Rules (2 copies), 1982 (Box 25, Folder 96)
  - The Completeness of Provable Realizability (2 copies), 1989 (Box 25, Folder 97)
  - Reduction of finite and infinite derivations, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 98)
  - Reduction to Theories of Lower Order, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 99)
  - Reflection and Transfinite Induction (2 copies), undated (Box 25, Folder 100)
  - Resolution Calculi fro Modal Logics (2 copies), 1989 (Box 25, Folder 101)
  - Resolution Calculus for the First Order Linear Logic (2 copies), 1993 (Box 25, Folder 102)
  - Resolution Strategies for the Intuitionistic Logic (3 copies), 1994 (Box 25, Folder 103)
  - Semantics of a Declarative Language, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 104)
  - Computers and Artificial Intelligence, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 105)
  - Skolem's Method of Elimination of Positive Quantifiers in Sequential Calculi (2 copies), 1966 (Box 25, Folder 106)
  - Solvability of the Problem of Deducibility in LJ for a Class of Formulas not Containing Negative Occurrences of Quantifiers (2 copies), undated (Box 25, Folder 107)
  - Some formal systems of the logic programming, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 108)
  - Strong Termination for the Epsilon Substitution Method (2 copies), 1996 (Box 25, Folder 109)
  - Stability of E-theorems and Program Verification (7 copies), undated (Box 25, Folder 110)
  - What Can Be Done in PRA, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 111)
  - Transfer of Sequent Calculus Strategies to Resolution for S4 (2 copies), 1996 (Box 25, Folder 112)
  - Three Faces of Natural Deduction (2 copies), 1997 (Box 25, Folder 113)
  - The Universality of the Canonical Tree (2 copies), 1976 (Box 25, Folder 114)
  - The Use of Abstract Language in Elementary Metamathematics: Some Pedagogic Examples, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 115)
  - The complexity of the disjunction and existential properties in intuitionistic logic (2 copies), 1998 (Box 25, Folder 116)
  - The Epsilon Substitution Method and Continuity (2 copies), 2002 (Box 25, Folder 117)
  - The Independence of the Postulates of Natural Calculi, undated (Box 25, Folder 118)
  - The Skolem Method in Intuitionistic Calculi, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 119)
  - The PRIZ system and Propositional Calculus, 0 (Box 25, Folder 120)
  - Friedman, Harvey (Box 43)
- Subject files
  - Partial Copies, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - B3AAA4AX, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Halmosh, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - J.V. Neumann, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Schwichtenberg and Wainer, undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Trakhtenbrot and Barzdin, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - V. Dalen Brouwer, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Moschovakis, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Normann, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Walters, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Mitchell, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Lyndon, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Leisenring, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Lewis and Papa, undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Thinking About Mathematics, undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Gentzen, undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Girard, 10/29/2009 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Jervell, 4/17/2009 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Fitting and Smullyan, undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Krantz, 7/25/2007 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Harrison, undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Kunen, undated (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Girard, undated (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Edwards, undated (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Pohlers, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Lambda-calculus and Combinators in the 20th Century, 7/24/2009 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - RPR Handouts (my copies), 6/13/2000 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Provability Logic, 38292 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Using the Borsuk-Ulam Theorem, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Shoenfild, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Thinking About Mathematics, undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Epsilon, 2000-2001 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Epsilon, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Epsilon, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Epsilon, 1995-1997 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Epsilon, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Workbooks, 2005-2006 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Epsilon, undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Epsilon, 2001-2005 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Papadi, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Epgytest, undated (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Epsotransp, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Epsilon and Henry, undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - A New Approach to Epsilon-Substitution Method, 37245 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Epsilon Substitution Method for ID1, 17-18 Jan. (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - von Neumann's Example, 38203 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - APAL Paper, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Migoa Report Etc., undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Epgy, undated (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - M294 Epsilon, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Workbooks, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Epsilon, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Epsilon, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Epsilon, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - A New Approach to Epsilon-Substitution Method, 36944 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Normalization, undated (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Normalization, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Epsilon, undated (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Epsilon, Oct. 1991 - Feb. 1992 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Epsilon-Symbol, 1983 - July 1991 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Akiyoshi Ryota, undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - KO^M/APAR., undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Arai, undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Aczel, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Ackermann, undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Avigad, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Baaz, undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Beklemishev, 2011 Mar. (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Barendregt, undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Babaev, undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Brouwer, undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Bovykin, undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Beeson, undated (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Buss, undated (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Buchholz, undated (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Coquand, undated (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Ciabattoni, undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Carlson, undated (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Cantini, undated (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Corsi, undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Delzell, undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Ferreira, undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Fernandez, undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Dragalin/ Pap., undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Fitting, undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Fisher, undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Gabbay, undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Gavril, undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Ghilardi, undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Girard, undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Gurevich, undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Gowers, undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Gordeev, undated (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Hrubevs, undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Hirsch, undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Kaye, undated (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Jager, undated (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Sieg, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Shanin, undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Simpson, undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Scott D., undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Seely, undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Feferman, undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Van Benthem, undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Troelstra, undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Trakhtenbrot, undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Towsner, undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Taitslin, undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Takeuti, undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Wilken, undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Urquhart, undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Tseitin, undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Tupailo, undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Visser, undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Voevodsky, undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Voronkov, undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Statman, undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Slavnov, undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Sommer, undated (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Tait, undated (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Tatsuta, undated (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Tao, undated (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Wainer, undated (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Weiermann, undated (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Ting, undated (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Olkhovikov, undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Pappinghaus, undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Oliva, 40626 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Okada, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Parikh, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Parsons, undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Pauly, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Pearce, undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Plato, undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Zach, undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Zaslavsky, undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Zakhryashev, undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - McCarthy, 1978-1981 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Martin, undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Miller, undated (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Moschovakis, undated (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Leivant, undated (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Leitgeb, undated (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Levin, undated (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Lifschitz, undated (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Kopke, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Heusinger, undated (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Harrison, undated (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Hales, undated (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Lando, 2011 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Kripke, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Lambek, undated (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Maslov, undated (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Wilken, undated (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Wolter, undated (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Manin, 2011 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Maksimova, undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Nerode, undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Muravitski, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Mundici, undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Kohlenbach, undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Kohlenbach A-F, undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Kushner, undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Kohlenbach, 2010 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Kreisel, undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Kremer, undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Five Notes on the Application of Proof Theory to Computer Science, 12/10/1971 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Kreisel Elements, undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Fresh 12, undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Fresh, undated (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - PT 2012, 2010/2011 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - General Interest, 2008-2009 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Proof Mining, 2010 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Here There, 2009 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Ebar Transp., 2008 (Box 14, Folder 4)